so now let's see if we understood what
are all the things that happen in one
cycle in tomasulo's algorithm suppose
that this is the situation we have at
the beginning of a cycle we have an
instruction that is waiting to be issued
in the instruction queue this is the
contents of the Rat these are the values
for the
registers these are the reservation
stations two of them are occupied one is
still
available and the instruction in the
reservation station Zer is executing in
the ALU and during this cycle it will
broadcast its result which is
4.4 this is what is allowed to happen in
the same cycle issuing and then
dispatching the instruction cannot
happen in the same cycle capturing a
result and then dispatching can happen
in this particular
processor and then issuing and
broadcasting of a result for the same
rat entry is of course also allowed the
first part of this quiz is at the end of
the cycle whose beginning we are looking
at here what will be the content of the
two rat entries and the two registers so
after the end of this cycle what's going
to be here here here and here